# CHRISTOPHER "CJ" JOHNSON

# UX/UI Designer

## CONTACT

Johnsonce3101@gmail.com

Knoxville, TN

in My Profile

My Portfolio

# SKILLS

**Design Psychology** Front End -

Figma Web Development

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Research

Sketching

Data Synthesis

**Usability Testing Usability Testing** 

Journey Mapping

**Usability Testing** 

Journey Mapping

HTML

CSS

JavaScript (JS)

Node.js

Git

Bootstrap

Material UI

React.js

Angular.js

# EDUCATION

## UX/UI Design (Cert.)

V School

OCT 2022 - Current

#### Web Development (Cert.)

DigitalCrafts

APR 2021 - OCT 2021

# Intelligence & Technology (A.A.S)

Community College of the Air-force

JUL 2015 - DEC 2016

# Psychology (B.A.)

(Clinical)

East Tennessee State University

AUG 2010 - MAY 2015

### PROFILE

A passionate professional who balances combining elements of psychology, and design thinking to create products that fulfill the user's needs. Capable team player with an equal ability to take initiative and lead in order to get the job done. UX Researcher exploring user needs, pain point and behaviors.

### EXPERIENCE

# **Application Development Analyst**

Accenture (10/2021 - 10/2022)

- · Developed RICEFW solutions for client stakeholders using agile methodologies.
  - Provided timely data analysis for 10k+ defects to improve productivity
- · Certified in Salesforce (SF) Platform (Vlocity OmniStudio Developer & Consultant).

# **Brand Strategist**

NueWay Studios (08/2019 - 04/2020)

- · First point of contact for clients, guided clients through initial on boarding processes and branded marketing strategies.
- · Elevated customer experience engagement strategy
  - · lead to 50% contract signing increase.

#### **All-Source Intelligence Technician**

U.S. Air-Force (07/2015 - 07/2019)

- Assessed vulnerabilities of DoD cyberspace enterprise that could be exploited by adversaries.
- Reduced product completion from 3 months to 48 days.
- Conducted database research prepared intelligence reports and charts.
- · Supervision
  - · Team lead: Trained supervisors and co-worker on critical thinking, analytical writing skills, and presentation.
  - Trained team members of the importance of resilience.
  - · Emphasized organization of documentation regarding product research